surf2buy.in 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy

We thank you for your visit and the trust you place in Surf2Buy.in. We believe and strive for high customer data integrity/privacy and ensure that the standards for transactions are secure. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please leave your feedback to us. 

By mere use of the website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement.

**a. Information Collection**

We collect data to analyse and serve our customers better.            When you visit our site, we collect data on from which URL have you reached us and which URL are you going to. We also track the IP address. Cookies are enabled to track how you navigate in our website. We don’t control third party cookies. It is entirely on you to accept/reject third party cookies.

If you wish to register with us or when you transact with us, we ask for your addresses, which are billing or shipping. For making a transaction, the credit card details are done on the payment gateway or bank website. We don’t store the credit card details. 

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

  **b. Use of data collected**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website.

**c. Sharing of personal information**

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**d. Other Websites Links**

Our site links may link to other websites which may collect personally identifiable information about you. Surf2buy.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**e. Choice/Opt-Out**

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

**f. Advertisements on Surf2Buy.in**

We have third party advertising companies who display there ads on your visit to our website. They may use information about your visit however the name /address/email /telephone and other demographics details are kept confidential and not shared.

**g. Your Consent**

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**h. Grievance Handling**

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

                Harsh Bhatia

                M: 8904024365

                harshbhatia@surf2buy.com
